We're going to get into a roughly upright position, we're going to take our thumbs here, we're going to place them under this
我们将采取一个大致直立的姿势，将拇指放在这里，置于此
frequency,
频率之下，
and we're going to put that under our armpits, like so.
然后像这样将其置于腋下。
You're going to take a deep breath in through your nose,
您将通过鼻子进行一次深吸气，
a slightly straighter posture for the body, because we're going to work with the central channel.
身体姿态稍微更直立，因为我们将与中轴通道协同工作。
You inhale through your nose,
你通过鼻子吸气，
and you're going to exhale through your mouth the notion of self, your mental, egoistic toxins.
你将通过嘴巴呼出自我概念，以及你精神上的、自私的毒素。
You release them from yourself, so you inhale.
你将它们从你体内排出，然后你吸气。
You exhale the unnecessary from yourself.
你呼出你体内无用的东西。
You inhale.
你吸气。
One last time, you inhale.
再最后一次，你吸气。
To have clear awareness, you will now place your longest finger
为了获得清晰的意识，你现在将放置手指，
at the nasion.
将最长的手指放在鼻根点（nasion）处。
You will block your right nostril.
你将堵住右侧鼻孔。
You will.
你将开始。
Inhale with your left nostril.
用左侧鼻孔吸气。
And you will truly think that you are inhaling prana.
你要仔细思考你正在吸入生命能量（prana）。
So you concentrate on this level of prana.
所以你专注于这种生命能量（prana）的层面。
You inhale through your left nostril.
你通过左侧鼻孔吸气。
You block with the other side and exhale with your right nostril.
你用另一侧堵住，然后用右侧鼻孔呼气。
You re-inhale with your right nostril.
你再次用右侧鼻孔吸气。
You move and exhale through your left nostril.
你堵住，然后通过左侧鼻孔呼气。
You do one more cycle.
你再进行一个循环。
You inhale prana.
你吸入生命能量（prana）。
the air, the light, the vibration, through the left nostril, very
通过左侧鼻孔，轻轻地吸入空气、光、振动，
gently.
轻轻地。
You exhale through your right nostril.
你通过右侧鼻孔呼气。
You re-inhale once more through your right nostril.
你再次通过右侧鼻孔吸气。
You exhale through your left nostril.
你通过左侧鼻孔呼气。
You do it one last time.
你再做最后一次。
You gently inhale through your left nostril.
你轻轻地通过左鼻孔吸气。
You exhale through your right nostril.
你通过右鼻孔呼气。
little by little if you do this
渐渐地，如果你这样做
from time to time
不时地
you will open two small channels here
你会在那里打开两个小通道
it will open the sinus space
这将打开鼻窦空间
and it will open the clarity of thought
并开启思维的清晰度
we must open the central channel
我们必须打开中脉
for that we will do it with
为此，我们将通过
a pressure of prana
普拉那的压力
we're going to do a mulabandha
我们将做一个穆拉班达
that means we're going to contract the perineum
这意味着我们将进行会阴收缩
we're going to inhale first
我们将首先吸气
we're going to do a mulabandha
我们将做一个穆拉班达
we inflate here, then I contract the perineum,
我们在这里鼓起，然后我进行会阴收缩，
I pull in my stomach and lift my diaphragm to bring the air upwards,
我收腹并提升横膈膜，以将气团向上提升，
I tuck my chin, I close my glottis,
我收下巴，关闭声门，
and I gradually bring a sensation as if I were bringing this pressure to open here.
我渐渐地带来一种感觉，仿佛我正在施加这种压力以打开这里。
We inhale, we bring the pranic air into the belly,
我们吸气，将普拉那气团带入腹部，
you pull in, you do a small pelvic tilt, you close the glottis,
你收腹，做一点骨盆倾斜，关闭声门，
You tilt and raise the diaphragm to the top.
你倾斜并提升横膈膜直到顶部。
And you release.
然后你放松。
There, you open your central channel in the form of a symbol.
在这里，你以符号的形式打开你的中脉。
You inhale once more.
你再一次吸气。
Last time, I inhale.
最后一次，我吸气。
Now, you completely empty the air, as much as you can, and
现在，你完全排出空气，尽可能多地，并且
at the end, through the void, you raise your diaphragm, like
最后，在排空后，你提升你的横膈膜，像
this, and then you lower it, I'll show you.
这样，然后你让它下降，我给你演示。
It will warm up the body a bit
这会使身体稍微温暖
and at the same time you open things up a little
同时你也会稍微打开一些通道
you're just going to take your hands
你只需握住双手
and you're going to open and stretch a bit
然后稍微打开并伸展
all the meridians
所有经络
to have your hands open
以便双手充分打开
and your body ready to work
身体准备好工作
like this
就像这样
We bring the chi into our hands.
我们将气引入手中。
There, you enter a meditative state that you can.
好的，你进入一种冥想状态。
And you close your eyes.
然后闭上眼睛。
And you become aware of prana.
感受生命能量（Prana）的存在。
Prana as a means, as a vehicle.
生命能量（Prana）作为一种媒介，一种载体。
You remember that prana is air.
你要记住，生命能量（Prana）就是空气。
It is this light and it is this energy in the form
它是这种光，是这种能量，以
of a vibration.
振动的形式存在。
Somewhere, you are nourished by prana.
在某种程度上，你被生命能量（Prana）滋养着。
If you become aware of this quality, you
如果你意识到这种品质，你将
will become aware of what we call the whole.
意识到我们所说的“整体”。
If you become aware of your breathing in this three-dimensionality,
如果你在这三维空间中意识到你的呼吸，
you become...
你就成为...
the whole. In fact, it's so simple that we don't do it. In a way,
整体。事实上，这太简单了，以至于我们没有去做。在某种
we can say
程度上，我们可以说
that healing, it is the healing of illness, it
疗愈，也就是疾病的疗愈，是
is an awakening. At some point, you will no longer
一种意识的觉醒。在某个时刻，你将不再
speak of illness, but you will speak of a low vibration. So if you know how to
谈论疾病，而是谈论一种低频振动。所以如果你知道如何
increase your vibration, if you know how to increase this frequency, you
提升你的振动，如果你知道如何提高这种频率，你将
will have healing. That's why
会获得疗愈。这是为了
but as a therapist, you must always increase your vibration, or
但作为一名治疗师，你必须始终提升你的振动，或者
neutralize it.
中和它。
You must increase it so that you become untouchable.
你必须提升它，这样你才能变得像不可触及一样。
You shouldn't specifically perceive this detail, otherwise we fall into pride.
不要特别关注这个细节，否则我们会陷入傲慢。
In the end, you also have to give everything, give everything back.
在最后，也要全然付出，全然回馈。
That's where we need to be in non-willingness.
这就是我们必须处于无为状态的地方。
In a way,
在某种程度上，
Whether we are aware of it or not, we go through prana.
无论我们是否有意识，我们都经历着产前状态。
Be in the time of non-judgment.
处于无评判的时间里。
And there, the patient will ask you to place yourself at the level that will ultimately suit them
届时，患者会要求您将自己置于最终适合他的层面，
best.
最合适的。
It can be visceral, cranial, vertebral, anything.
这可以是内脏的、颅骨的、脊柱的，任何方面。
You just have to listen and follow the present movement.
你只需倾听并跟随当下的律动。
In a way, the only thing that exists is harmony.
在某种程度上，唯一存在的就是和谐。
And harmony is achieved through the complementarity of duality in the extension
而和谐是通过二元性的互补性，在延续中获得，
of the equality of the other.
即他者的平等。
Often, it is pride to give an answer before the question.
通常，在问题之前给出答案是一种傲慢。
Often, without realizing it, we create points of support, we create question marks for the patient.
通常，在不知不觉中，我们为患者制造了支点，制造了疑问。
Free yourself from that.
摆脱它。
Man does not create his illness, he suffers it.
人并非创造疾病，而是承受疾病。
It is a response to the question that, more or less consciously, he has asked himself.
它是对患者或多或少有意识地提出的问题的回应。
Breathe not by your will, the will to help the other which
不要通过你的意志呼吸，那种帮助他人的意志，它
ultimately can harm more than it helps.
最终可能弊大于利。
Breathe prana, increase your vibration.
呼吸产前状态，提升你的振动频率。
One way to increase your vibration is to try to become aware that
提升振动频率的一种方式是尝试意识到
every word is a vibration.
每个词语都是一种振动。
Eliminate from your vocabulary as much as possible words that have a low.
尽可能地从你的词汇中消除那些低频的词语。
you will clean your inner diamond. That's where you need to become conscious. Every
你将清洁你的内在钻石。这就是需要变得有意识的地方。每一个
word,
词语，
every gesture, every look, is a vibration. Increase your vibration. It's
每一个姿态，每一个眼神，都是一种振动。提升你的振动频率。这
as if the
就像是
earth needed it. Be like weavers of light. Every
地球需要它。成为光的编织者。每一次
time you have a thought,
当你有一个念头时，
it goes into the akasha and is distributed in the great web. We
它会进入阿卡莎（Akasha），并被分布到巨大的网络中。我们
have a right to this consciousness.
享有这种意识。
There, you can feel a vibration in your heart, like little
此时，您可能会在您的心脏中感受到一种振动，就像微小的搏动。
tingles.
petits  pétiments.